JAMES LEE

Senior Software Engineer

SUMMARY

Technically-sound GIS Engineer effective in analyzing relevant information and guiding product cycle from conception to completion. 4 years of experience in developing ESRI GIS projects and 3 years in web applications using Arcobjects, geoprocessing tools and server object extensions. Strong understanding of Object Oriented Languages, Object Oriented Application Development(OOAD), and Database design (RDBMS) and GUI design, Good understanding of End user req. analysis and full software development Life Cycle.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

06/2018 - 03/2020

Recursive

Shibuya City, Japan

- Performed troubleshooting, documentation and maintenance for clients Generated reports using Live Project reporting tool.
- Assisted in weather forecast application development for local news channels Involved in research and analysis of industrial pollution survey and built the map after compilation of data
- Designed and developed GIS application for various enterprises and business units
 Created a data integration interface to compile data from different formats into a single graphical format

Software Engineer

11/2016 - 06/2018

Mezurashico Ota City, Japan

- Coordinated with ICT staff for installation and maintenance of software
 Completed all projects within the timeline and allocated budget
- Developed a custom module to integrate satellite image processing systems with cloud
- Developed a custom module to integrate satellite image processing systems with cloud computing
- Created data integration component to import data from non image formats to GIS
 imaging application without loss of data or image quality during transit and conversion
- Involved in expressway development project and designed the new eight lane expressway model for the State Highway and Expressway Development Association

Junior Engineer

09/2014 - 11/2016

Pangeanic

Chiyoda City, Japan

- Assisted in debugging over 100+ bugs, to accelerate testing and development of an essential web-based product
- Perform HR data collection and a variety of statistical analyses using Microsoft Excel, SAS, Tableau and Python.
- · Worked in a team of 4 people under agile conditions

LANGUAGES

English

Proficient

••••

EDUCATION

BS: Computer Science

Nagoya University 2011 - 2014

GPA | 3.6 / 4.0

TECH STACK

Programming Languages

Python · R · Javascript · CSS ·

Bootstrap · XML · HTML5

GIS

Arcmap · Arcobjects · ArcGIS Server ·

Geoprocessing

Database

 $\mathsf{MSSQL} \cdot \mathsf{MySQL} \cdot \mathsf{PostgreSQL} \cdot$

MongoDB · Apache Cassandra

Others

AWS · Azure · GIT · Machine Learning

